A Guide to the Near East Foundation records Accessions 2009.104, 2010.002, 2010.020 FA406
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2009.104: Near East Foundation records, 1915-2003; 1940-1980; AC 2009:104; 180 Cubic Feet 168 boxes, including 150 standard record storage boxes
  - Personnel/Contracts
    - Contract - Dale M. Reeves - Ghana (Box 14)
    - Personal - Dale M. Reeves - Ghana (Box 14)
    - Contract - Reid, J. Martin, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Reid, J. Martin - Mali, 1967-1980 (Box 14)
    - Reyna, Stephan, P., Ph.D., 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - Reames, Herman M., 1978-1979 (Box 14)
    - Rice, Laura W. (Mrs. Robert P.), 1983-1985 (Box 14)
    - Reid, J. Martin, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
    - Robert P. Rice, Jr., 1983-1986 (Box 14)
    - Personnel - Genevieve Richardson, 1947 (Box 14)
    - Roberts, Luther H. - Ethopia, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - Contract - Roberts, Luther H., 1973-1975 (Box 14)
    - West Cameroon - TDY Vegetable - Dr. R. Wayne Robinson, 1966-1967 (Box 14)
    - Raymond Wayne Robinson, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Willard Robinson - Contract File, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - Robinson, Willard S., 1980-1981 (Box 14)
    - Willard S. Robinson - Bee Specialist, 1980-1982 (Box 14)
    - Jordan - Bee Project - Dr. Willard S. Robinson, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Mary S. Roche - Jordan, 1981-1986 (Box 14)
    - Personnel - Rodgers, Horace C. Jr., 1954-1966 (Box 14)
    - Personal - Joe B. Richardson - Libya, 1967-1976 (Box 14)
    - Conract - Joe B. Richardson, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Rodgers, Horace C. Jr. - Iran, 1975-1979 (Box 14)
    - Contract - Rodgers, Horace C., 1975 (Box 14)
    - Mr. Horace C. Rodgers, Jr., 1963-1983 (Box 14)
    - Contract - Rodgers, Horace C. Jr., 1953-1958 (Box 14)
    - Romeieh, June H., 1978-1980 (Box 14)
    - Stephen roush - Jordan, 1977-1983 (Box 14)
    - Jordan - Personal File - Stephen Roush, 1977-1983 (Box 14)
    - Wm. J. Russell - Lesotho, 1977-1979 (Box 14)
    - William J. Russell - Agronomist - Tanzania, 1967-1974 (Box 14)
    - Personal - William J. Russell - Libya, 1974 (Box 14)
    - William J. Russell - Lebanon, 1977-1983 (Box 14)
    - Lebanon - William Russell - Personal File, 1980-1983 (Box 14)
    - Personal - Charles Rust - Africa, 1966-1970 (Box 15)
    - Charles Henry Rust, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - "S" General, 1951-1953 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - Saeedy, Ali, 1952-1953 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - Prof. Salisbury, 1946 (Box 15)
    - Salk, Steven M. Tanzania, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
    - Contract - Salk, Steven M., 1975 (Box 15)
    - Kent Salter, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - Sam, M., 1954-1955 (Box 15)
    - Personal - Victor Theodore Sander, 1956-1964 (Box 15)
    - Contract - Victor Theodore Sander, 1959 April 12 - 1961 April 11 (Box 15)
    - Personal - Benjamin Sann - Tanzania, 1972-1975 (Box 15)
    - Contract - Benjamin Sann, 1974 (Box 15)
    - M.S.A. El Sarrag - Sudan, 1982-1985 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - Margaret Scanlan, 1944-1946 (Box 15)
    - Scanlan, Margaret - Contract, 1943-1947 (Box 15)
    - Contract - Donald J. Luebbe, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Kenya - Rural Development Officer - Kirk W. Lund, 1954-1967 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - Lund, Kirk, 1954-1967 (Box 15)
    - Contract - Lund, Kirk W., 1954-1956 (Box 15)
    - Contract - Luster, George L. (Iran), 1962 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - Luster, George (Iran), 1962-1978 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - Lynch, Matthew C. (Iran), 1955-1969 (Box 15)
    - Contract - Lynch, Matthew C. (Iran), 1964-1965 (Box 15)
    - Rosemarie Lynch, 1974-1987 (Box 15)
    - Katharine Lyons, 1946 (Box 15)
    - "M", 1947-1948 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - Makris, Aristides, 1953 (Box 15)
    - Madland, Marc P., 1975-1979 (Box 15)
    - Contract - Madland, Marc - Lesotho, 1976-1979 (Box 15)
    - Madland, Marc - Lesotho, 1976-1979 (Box 15)
    - Marc P. Madland - Mauritania - Animal Science, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Madland, Marguerite P., 1975-1978 (Box 15)
    - Madland, Marguerite - Personnel & Agreement, 1975-1979 (Box 15)
    - Mallory, Mr. Dale - Claim File - Blue Cross & Blue Shield, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
    - Contract - Dale R. Mallory - Iran, 1972-1974 (Box 15)
    - Personnel - Dale R. Mallory - Iran, 1971-1976 (Box 15)
    - Personal - Mann, William, Jr. - Ghana, 1957-1980 (Box 16)
    - Contract - Mann, William Jr. - Ghana, 1957-1960 (Box 16)
    - Personnel - March, Frank A., 1954-1959 (Box 16)
    - Dr. Deran Markarian - INA Appl. Blank, 1978 (Box 16)
    - Contract - Markarian, Deran, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - Markarian, Dr. Deran - Agronomist, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
    - Markarian, Deran Ph.D. - Agronomist, 1975-1979 (Box 16)
    - Scherer, Leroy F. - Lesotho, 1975-1978 (Box 16)
    - Contract - Scherer, Leroy F., 1975-1981 (Box 16)
    - Scherer, Leroy, 1975-1978 (Box 16)
    - Personal - Ervin W. Schleicher, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Ervin W. Scheicher - Kenya/FOA Contract, 1969-1970 (Box 16)
    - Schleicher, Ervin W. - Contract, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Personal - Schepmoes, Lindsley, 1966 (Box 16)
    - Personal - W.J. Schmid - Tanzania - Irrigation Engineer, 1968-1971 (Box 16)
    - Personnel - Schmid, William J., 1934-1963 (Box 16)
    - Agrarian - Schmid, William Joseph - Technical Service Specialist, 1954-1956 (Box 16)
    - Contract - Wiliam Joseph Schmid - Tanzania, 1966 (Box 16)
    - Schmidt, Erneset Carl, 1976-1979 (Box 16)
    - Schwartz, John J., 1957-1960 (Box 16)
    - Personal - F. Grant Scott - Iran, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Scott, Forest Grant (Africa), 1962-1971 (Box 16)
    - Contract - F. Grant Scott - Iran, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Contract - Scott, Gorest Grant (Africa) - Agricult. Ext. Advisor - Central Africa Republic, 1964 (Box 16)
    - Personnel - Scranton, 1946 (Box 16)
    - Michaelides Scurso, 1953-1970 (Box 16)
    - Clyde C. Searl - Contract, Lome, Togo, 1978 (Box 16)
    - Personal - Clyde C. Searl - Africa, 1967 (Box 16)
    - Personal - Clyde C. Searl - Morocco, 1969-1978 (Box 16)
    - Contract - Clyde C. Searl - Morocco, 1970-1979 (Box 17)
    - Searl, Clyde Cromwell - Contract, 1967 (Box 17)
    - Searl, Mr. Clyde C. - Claim File, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
    - Searl, Clyde - Folder #3, 1980 (Box 17)
    - Searl, Clyde C. - Folder #2 - Rural Development - Togo, 1977 October (Box 17)
    - Searl, Clyde C., 1977 (Box 17)
    - Searl, Clyde - Tanzania (Box 17)
    - Personal - Leon Oscar Selle, 1967 (Box 17)
    - Selle, Leon Oscar - Contract, 1967 (Box 17)
    - Shanahan, Anne, 1977-1979 (Box 17)
    - Personnel - Shook, Vernon P., 1954-1958 (Box 17)
    - Contract - Shook, Vernon P. (Abscent) (Box 16)
    - Contract - Shook, Vernon P., 1954-1958 (Box 17)
    - Personal - John T. Short, 1972 (Box 17)
    - Contract - John T. Short, 1972 (Box 17)
    - Sandra G. Sieber - Lesotho, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
    - Personnel - Olga Sigi, 1975-1977 (Box 17)
    - Singleton, 1975-1977 (Box 17)
    - Singleton, Dr. Carey B., Jr. - Agricultural Economist (Livestock Planner), 1975-1977 (Box 17)
    - Personal - Joseph Slade - Africa - Kenya - Range Mgt. Adv., 1966-1976 (Box 17)
    - Joseph Wilford Slade, 1967 (Box 17)
    - Agrarian - Slaugh, Kimbal George - Rural Credit Specialist, 1954-1956 (Box 17)
    - Personnel - Slaugh, Kimball G., 1954-1956 (Box 17)
    - Agricultural Engineer - Willis Henry Sletten - File No. 2, 1954-1972 (Box 17)
    - Agricultural Engineer - Willis H. Sletten - File No. 1 - Iran, 1954-1972 (Box 17)
    - Smith, Charles O. - b. '27 - Vocational Agri. & R. Development, 1973-1978 (Box 17)
    - Contract - Smith, James E., 1974 (Box 17)
    - Smith, James E. - Botswana, 1973-1979 (Box 17)
    - Meverette Smith, 1943-1947 (Box 17)
    - Personal - Paul L. Smith - Libya, 1968-1979 (Box 17)
    - Contract - Paul L. Smith - Libya, 1968 (Box 17)
    - Smith, Wesley S. - Agricultural Adm., 1975 (Box 17)
    - Personnel - Smither, Robert T., 1954-1973 (Box 17)
    - Agrarian - Smither, Robert Ray - Community Development Specialist, 1954-1956 (Box 17)
    - Contract - Rita Snook, 1969 (Box 17)
    - Personal - Rita Snook, 1969 (Box 17)
    - Personal - Snyder, Walter E. (Libya), 1969-1979 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Dr. Walter E. Snyder - University of Libya, 1969 (Box 18)
    - Personal - Lorell Sorensen - Africa, 1965-1981 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Sorensen, Lorell L. (Togo), 1966-1968 (Box 18)
    - Personal - Mr. Curtis J. Spalding, 1968 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Spalding, Curtis J., 1968-1969 (Box 18)
    - Personnel - Spalding, Curtis J., 1951-1975 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Spalding, Curtis J., 1953-1957 (Box 18)
    - Personnel - Spalding, Orpha, 1958-1961 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Spalding, Orpha (Mrs. Curtis J.), 1951-1957 (Box 18)
    - Personal - William Homer Stacy, 1957-1973 (Box 18)
    - Contract - William Homer Stacy, 1959 August 10 - 1961 August 9 (Box 18)
    - Stanley, Richard J. - Tanzania, 1973-1977 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Stanley, Richard J., 1974 (Box 18)
    - Personnel - Stefanson, Hal, 1954-1956 (Box 18)
    - Agrarian - Stefanson, Hal - Rural Credit Specialist, 1954-1956 (Box 18)
    - Ag. Exten.: M.F. Stelzer - Cameroon, 1956-1966 (Box 18)
    - Personnel - Stelzer, Milton F., 1956-1979 (Box 18)
    - Stephanides, C.S. - Contract File, 1944 (Box 18)
    - Personal - Dr. Mary Stephano, 1969-1973 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Dr. Mary Stephano, 1971 (Box 18)
    - Personal - Kenneth W. Stokes, 1970-1975 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Kenneth W. Stokes, 1970-1973 (Box 18)
    - Personal - Swecker, John B. - Lesotho, 1972-1980 (Box 18)
    - Personnel - "T" General, 1946-1951 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Swecker, John B., 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - David C. Tarbox - Claim File INA, 1978 (Box 18)
    - Tarbox, David - Lesotho, 1976-1979 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Tarbox, David, 1976 November (Box 18)
    - Personal - Forrest P. Tassin, Jr., 1967 (Box 18)
    - Tassin, Forrest P. - Contract, 1967 (Box 18)
    - Tates, Edward W. - Mechanical Maintenance, 1975-1978 (Box 18)
    - Contract - Tates, Edwards W., 1975-1976 (Box 19)
    - Personal - Taylor, James W. (Africa) - Horticulturist - Dahomey, 1965-1977 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Taylor, James W. (Africa) - Horticulturist - Dahomey, 1965-1969 (Box 19)
    - Personal - Donald James Terp, 1959-1964 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Donald James Terp, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Personnel - Theodoridou, Vassiliki, 1951-1952 (Box 19)
    - Personnel - Theodoridou, Nicholos, 1945-1950 (Box 19)
    - Personnel - Theodorou, Nicholos, 1935-1941 (Box 19)
    - Personal - Evan C. Thompson - Tanzania, 1967-1972 (Box 19)
    - Thompson, Evan C. - Contract, 1968 (Box 19)
    - Robert C. Thompson TO22 - Beef Production Technician, 1971-1980 (Box 19)
    - Personal - Robert C. Thompson, 1972 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Robert C. Thompson, 1972 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Thomsen, John C. (Dr.), 1977 (Box 19)
    - Thomsen, John C. (Dr.) - Tanzania, 1979-1980 (Box 19)
    - Mr. John Thomsen - Claim File, 1979 (Box 19)
    - Personnel - Towne, Kathryn, 1952 (Box 19)
    - Irving Townsend, 1969-1971 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Irving D. Townsend, 1969 (Box 19)
    - Truby, Margaret Johnson, 1943-1945 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Truitt, Jack P., 1951-1952 (Box 19)
    - Personnel - Truitt, John, 1951-1958 (Box 19)
    - Valentine, Joan E., 1978-1983 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Vance, E. Pershing, 1977 (Box 19)
    - Vance, E. Pershing - Tanzania, 1977 (Box 19)
    - Vance, E. Pershing - Lesotho, 1971-1979 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Vance, E. Pershing, 1974 (Box 19)
    - Vance, E. Pershing, 1977-1980 (Box 19)
    - Personnel - Vandrell, Earl F., 1956-1971 (Box 19)
    - Vandrell, Earl F. [unlabeled], 1972-1982 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Vandrell, Earl, 1957-1958 (Box 20)
    - Earl F. Vandrell, 1972 (Box 19)
    - Contract - Van Vorrthuizen E.G., 1974 (Box 20)
    - Personal - Van Voorthuizen, Evert G. - Range Management Advisor / Africa Upper Volta - File 2, 1964-1967 (Box 20)
    - Personal - E.G. Van Voorthuizen - Tanzania, 1967-1972 (Box 20)
    - Contract - Van Voorthuizen, Evert G. (Africa) - Range Management Advisor - Upper Volta, 1964-1967 (Box 20)
    - Dr. Lowenstein, 1974-1977 (Box 20)
    - Contract - Evert G. Van Voorthuizen, 1969 (Box 20)
    - Contract - Travis T. Voelke, 1975 (Box 20)
    - Voelkel File, 1971-1977 (Box 20)
    - Personal - Travis Voelkel, 1969 (Box 20)
    - Contract - Travis Voelkel, 1969 (Box 20)
    - O'Donnell & Weyher (Lawyers) Voelkel, Travis, 1977 (Box 20)
    - Personal - Travis T. Voelkel, 1975 (Box 20)
    - Contract - Vorhis, Robert C., 1979 (Box 20)
    - Vorhis, Robert C. Tanzania, 1976-1979 (Box 20)
    - Vorhis, Robert C. - Tanzania #2 (see also File #1), 1977-1979 (Box 20)
    - Vorhis, Robert C., 1976-1979 (Box 20)
    - Personnel - "W" General, 1942-1953 (Box 20)
    - Wallace, John G., 1980-1981 (Box 20)
    - John G. Wallace - Rabbit Production, 1977-1981 (Box 20)
    - Personnel - Warren, Mrs. Ruth, 1954 (Box 20)
    - Contract - Warren, Mrs. Ruth, 1954 (Box 20)
    - Personal - Barrie D. Watson, 1971-1975 (Box 20)
    - Barrie D. Watson - 21 - Research Officer (Vet), 1971-1975 (Box 20)
    - Contract - Barrie D. Watson, 1972 (Box 20)
    - John Weatherson - Swaziland, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Contract - Weber, Fred R. - Forestry Advisor - Niger, 1964-1966 (Box 20)
    - Personal - Weber, Fred R. - Africa, 1962-1967 (Box 20)
    - Mary Ales Welbaum, 1981-1983 (Box 20)
    - Whipple, Clayton E., 1946-1982 (Box 20)
    - Charles T. White - Personal, 1956-1977 (Box 20)
    - Contract - White, Charles T., 1955-1959 (Box 20)
    - Personal - Charles T. White, 1968 (Box 21)
    - Personal - Larry D. White, 1967 (Box 21)
    - White, Larry D. - Contract, 1967-1969 (Box 21)
    - Whitman, Arthur H., 1976-1978 (Box 21)
    - Ruth B. Whittemore - Contract File, 1944-1947 (Box 21)
    - Personal - Wilderman, Leo C., 1965-1967 (Box 21)
    - Personal - Williams, D. Elizabeth (Iran) (Home Economist), 1953-1968 (Box 21)
    - Contract - Williams, D. Elizabeth (Miss), 1963-1966 (Box 21)
    - Personnel - Williams, John R., 1953-1966 (Box 21)
    - Contract - William, John R., 1953-1955 (Box 21)
    - Minnie Lee Hart Williams, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Personnel - Williams, Mrs. R.B., 1943-1956 (Box 21)
    - Personal - Williams, Raiford (Africa - Cameroon) - Poultry - Livestock Advisor, 1962-1976 (Box 21)
    - Patricia A. Williams, 1984-1986 (Box 21)
    - Personnel - "K" General, 1953 (Box 21)
    - Kaiser, Helen L., 1945-1946 (Box 21)
    - Kaiser, Helen Louise, 1945-1947 (Box 21)
    - Personnel - Kanalz, Jack P., 1956-1968 (Box 21)
    - Contract - Kanalz, Jack P., 1956-1958 (Box 21)
    - Kaufman, Jacques A., 1979 (Box 21)
    - Jacques A. Kaufman - Contract File, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Personal - Jacques A. Kaufman, 1967 (Box 21)
    - Kaufman, Jacques A. - Contract, 1967 (Box 21)
    - Personal - Dean Keith - Iran, 1967 (Box 21)
    - Richard Dean Keith - Contract, 1967 (Box 21)
    - Elise S. Kelly, 1980-1989 (Box 21)
    - Kukowshi, Gary E. - Tanzania, 1975-1979 (Box 21)
    - Khouri, Hana -Jordan, 1957-1981 (Box 21)
    - David L. Ketcham - write-ups, etc., 1965-1978 (Box 21)
    - Personal - Ketcham, David L. (Africa) - (Malagasy) Project Supervisor, 1968 (Box 21)
    - Contract - David L. Ketcham, 1965-1968 (Box 21)
    - Agriculture - Hana Khouri A-4, 1952-1958 (Box 21)
    - Contract - King, Uriel Milo, 1954-1958 (Box 21)
    - Personnel - King, Mrs. Ada L., 1955-1958 (Box 21)
    - King, Mrs. Ada Lila, 1954-1956 (Box 21)
    - Sam Kliger, 1971-1972 (Box 22)
    - Personnel - Dr. Samuel Kliger - Iran, 1971-1972 (Box 22)
    - Contract - Dr. Samuel Kliger, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Knapp, Merrill - Contract File, 1943 (Box 22)
    - Koch, Kenneth A., 1952-1959 (Box 22)
    - Contract - Koch, Kenneth A., 1951 (Box 22)
    - Apostolos Koskinides - Enclosed Material from Director of Development Files, 1961-1964 (Box 22)
    - Kopp, Daniel R. - Contract, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
    - Personal - Daniel R. Kopp - Africa, 1967-1979 (Box 22)
    - Personnel - King, Uriel M., 1956-1967 (Box 22)
    - Contract - Kukowski, Gary E., 1975 (Box 22)
    - Dr. Carl F. Kraenzel, 1954-1959 (Box 22)
    - Personnel - Kraenzel, Carl F., 1953-1966 (Box 22)
    - Koskinides - Greece - School for Deaf, 1963-1965 (Box 22)
    - Apostolos Koskinides, 1959-1960 (Box 22)
    - Biography of graduates from Mr. Koskinides, 1963 November (Box 22)
    - Koskinides, A., 1951-1967 (Box 22)
    - Contract - Koskinides, Apostolos, 1952-1960 (Box 22)
    - Koskinides, Apostolos, 1963-1980 (Box 22)
    - Theodore C. Kraenzel, 1960 (Box 22)
    - Personal - Kulp, Jack William - Ghana, 1957-1976 (Box 22)
    - Contract - Kulp, Jack William (Expiration), 1960 May 31 (Box 22)
    - Kerr, Samuel, 1957-1958 (Box 22)
    - Personnel - Kerr, Samuel, 1956-1968 (Box 22)
    - Kent, Ralph, 1945-1949 (Box 22)
    - Ralph Kent, 1945 (Box 22)
    - Khouri, Hana, 1969-1985 (Box 22)
    - Personnel - Hanna Khouri, 1952-1970 (Box 22)
    - Personnel - Khouri, Hanna, 1951 (Box 23)
    - Hanna A. Khouri, 1945-1949 (Box 23)
    - Khouri, Hanna - Personnel, 1950 (Box 23)
    - Personnel - "L" General, 1952-1977 (Box 23)
    - State Insurance Fund Laakonen Claim, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
    - William B. Laakonen - Egypt, 1982-1986 (Box 23)
    - Personnel - Lackey, Alvin S., 1954-1966 (Box 23)
    - Agrarian - Lackey, Alvin S. - Community Development Specialist, 1954-1959 (Box 23)
    - Personnel - Lackey, Vivian, 1955 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Lackey, Mrs. Vivian, 1954 (Box 23)
    - Landers, Linda L., 1978-1981 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Landers, Linda L., 1978 (Box 23)
    - Landers, Linda L. - Lebanon, 1978-1981 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Laforge, Melvin S., 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Laforge, Melvin S. - Kenya, 1975-1978 (Box 23)
    - Larnen, Kathleen M., 1976-1983 (Box 23)
    - Lewis, Irene, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Personnel - Jerry Larson - Ext. Advisor Hort. - Cameroon, 1965-1976 (Box 23)
    - Larson, Jerry Dale - Contract, 1967 (Box 23)
    - Robert J. LaTowsky - Consultant - Egypt, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
    - Lawson, Edward C. - Malawi, 1974-1980 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Lawson, Edward C., 1974-1975 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Leasure, Frederick G., 1941-1944 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Leasure, Lucy Olive Watkins, 1944-1945 (Box 23)
    - Personnel - Lerner, Mandel (Korea), 1961-1978 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Lewis, John Alfred (Korea), 1962-1965 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Lewis, John Alfred, 1956-1958 (Box 23)
    - Personnel - Lewis, John Alfred, 1956-1959 (Box 23)
    - Demetrius B. Lezos, 1952-1969 (Box 23)
    - Light, Darrell E. - Botswana, 1973-1979 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Light, Darrell, 1974-1979 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Lorrilliere, M. Katharine, 1940 (Box 23)
    - Loewenstein, Duane E., 1976-1978 (Box 23)
    - Loewenstein, Duane E., 1972-1981 (Box 23)
    - Personnel - Duane E. Loewenstein - Ghana (Box 23)
    - Contract - Dr. Duane E. Loewenstein - Ghana, 1972 August 11 (Box 23)
    - Contract - Duane E. Loewenstein, 1968-1979 (Box 23)
    - Loewenstein, Darleen E. - DBL1557, 1976 (Box 23)
    - Personal - Donald J. Luebbe - Kenya, 1970-1976 (Box 23)
    - Personnel - Leslie Jack Marks - Africa, 1967-1970 (Box 23)
    - Marks, Leslie J., 1967 (Box 23)
    - Agrarian - Martin, Calvin M. - Community Development Specialist, 1954-1956 (Box 23)
    - Personnel - Martin, Calvin Lee, 1954-1956 (Box 24)
    - Contract - Martin, James A., 1976-1978 (Box 24)
    - Martin, James A. - Tanzania, 1976-1979 (Box 24)
    - Martin, Neils L. Range Management, 1975-1977 (Box 24)
    - Contract - Marvel, Mason E., 1975 (Box 24)
    - Marvel, Mason Edwin - Ethopia, 1975-1981 (Box 24)
    - Elizabeth B. Mayston, 1983-1989 (Box 24)
    - Mayston - Personnel, 1950 (Box 24)
    - Heleln L. McCune, 1943 (Box 24)
    - Mayston, Elizabeth, 1945 (Box 24)
    - Personnel - Mayston, Elizabeth, 1953-1969 (Box 24)
    - Mayston, Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 24)
    - Personnel - Meaux, Gabriel C. (Africa) Agricult. Ext. Advisor - Dahomey, 1962-1976 (Box 24)
    - Contract - Meaux, Gabriel C. (Africa) Agricult. Ext. Advisor, 1964-1966 (Box 24)
    - Personal - Ralph L. Mendenall, 1969 (Box 24)
    - Contract - Ralph L. Mendenall - Jordan, 1969 (Box 24)
    - Contract - Merinar, Calvin C. - Iran, 1974 (Box 24)
    - Calvin C. Merinar, 1980 (Box 24)
    - Contract - Calvin C. Merinar - Uganda, 1971 (Box 24)
    - Merinar, Calvin C. - Incoming - Shipping Personal Effects, 1974 (Box 24)
    - Merinar, Calvin C. - Iran, 1974-1980 (Box 24)
    - Personal - Calvin C. Merinar (Uganda), 1970-1974 (Box 24)
    - Personnel - Miller, Clarence L., 1953-1958 (Box 24)
    - Personal - Clarence L. Miller, 1967-1979 (Box 24)
    - Contract - Clarence L. Miller, 1970-1972 (Box 24)
    - Contract - Miller, Clarence L., 1954-1955 (Box 24)
    - Personnel - Miller, Cora, 1952 (Box 24)
    - Mrs. E.C. Miller B/C & B/S Correspondence, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Personnel - Miller, E.C., 1951 (Box 24)
    - E.C. Miller - Speech Material, 1939 (Box 24)
    - Personnel - Miller, E.C. 1950 (Box 24)
    - Personnel - E.C. Miller, 1952-1965 (Box 24)
    - Personnel - Miller, Roy Mac, 1955-1965 (Box 24)
    - Contact - Miller, Roy Mac, 1955-1957 (Box 25)
    - Personal - Miller, Ruth, 1952-1957 (Box 25)
    - Flora A. Mitts - Contract, 1946 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Mizelle, James L., 1975-1978 (Box 25)
    - Mizelle, james L. - Mechanical Maintenance, 1975-1980 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Floyd D. Moon - Africa, 1967-1969 (Box 25)
    - Moon, Floyd D. - Bee Culture Specialist, 1977-1980 (Box 25)
    - Personnel - Floyd D. Moon - Africa, 1967 (Box 25)
    - James C. Moomaw, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Personnel - Moore, Ralph R., 1954-1975 (Box 25)
    - Agrarian - Moore, Ralph L. - Technical Service Specialist, 1954-1959 (Box 25)
    - Personnel - Moore, Robert, 1955-1965 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Moore, Robert L., 1956-1959 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Moris, Donald L., 1974-1976 (Box 25)
    - Personal - Donald L. Moris, 1970-1974 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Donald L. Moris, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Moris, Donald L. - Tanzania, 1971-1976 (Box 25)
    - Moris, Jon R. - Tanzania, 1971-1977 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Moris, Jon R., 1972-1976 (Box 25)
    - Personnel - Maurice B. Morrill, 1955-1976 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Maurice B. Morrill, 1960 July 25 - 1962 July 24 (Box 25)
    - Glenda Morrison, 1981-1982 (Box 25)
    - Personnel - Morrow, Robert B., 1954-1962 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Morrow, Robert B., 1954-1959 (Box 25)
    - Personnel - Morton, Madison H., 1955-1968 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Morton, Madison Hale, 1953-1957 (Box 25)
    - Personnel - Moussalli, J.F., 1953-1954 (Box 25)
    - Moustafa, Abdel M., 1977 (Box 25)
    - Moustafa, Dr. Abdel m. - Ethiopia, 1975-1980 (Box 25)
    - Contract - Moustafa, Dr. Abdel M., 1977 (Box 25)
    - Personal - Basil Moussouros, 1965-1977 (Box 25)
    - Basil Moussouros (Cornell University), 1945-1947 (Box 25)
    - Personnel - Mueller, Wilfred A., 1951 (Box 25)
    - Personnel - Mueller, Wilfred, 1952-1955 (Box 26)
    - Contract - Mueller, Wilfred A., 1951 (Box 26)
    - Muhr, Gilbert - Ethiopia, 1975-1977 (Box 26)
    - Contract - Muhr, Gilbert, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - Personal - John Mullenax, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Mullenax, John H. - Contract, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Dr. Harry Dierks Muller (Libya) - Fort Collins, Colorado - Poultry Science, Breeding, etc., 1968 (Box 26)
    - Contract - Muller, Robert G., 1976 (Box 26)
    - Muller, Robert D., 1975-1978 (Box 26)
    - Contract - H. Dale Munk, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Personnel - H. Dale Munk - Lesotho, 1973-1980 (Box 26)
    - Murphy, Mrs. Walter, 1958 (Box 26)
    - Murphy, Walter Lee - Contract, 1958 April 28 - 1960 April 27 (Box 26)
    - Murphy, Walter Lee - Personal, 1956-1964 (Box 26)
    - Personal - McCauley, John, 1955-1970 (Box 26)
    - Contract - McCauley, John P., 1954-1957 (Box 26)
    - Contract - McCellan, James W., 1976-1977 (Box 26)
    - McClellan, James W. - Well Drilling - b.23, 1975-1978 (Box 26)
    - Contract - MConnell, Charles B. - 1st - Botswana, 1974 (Box 26)
    - McConnell, Charles B. - Botswana 1st Contract, 1974-1978 (Box 26)